timecardcalculator.net 2014-06-30

# Time Card Calculator.net Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of TimeCardCalculator.net, The Company, owned and operated by Southborough Website Design at <http://southboroughwebsitedesign.com/>

Our postal address is   
PO Box 751  
Southborough, MA 01772

We can be reached via our postal address or you can reach us by telephone at 508-231-1331. 

In general, we receive two types of information from users:

**Personal Information:** In the form of return email addresses when a user sends electronic correspondence to us requesting specific information or to make a comment or request a calculator. We will only use this information to communicate regarding the request.

**Aggregated Information:** Information about users as a whole. The Company receives certain types of information about general activity at TimeCardCalculator.net. This does not include personal identifying information, but does include how many times TimeCardCalculator.net is visited, what pages or search terms are requested, what domain names (e.g. "aol.com") visitors are coming from and the date and time of each visit. The Company gathers and compiles this information into an aggregate form for statistical analysis and reporting. These reports track website activity overall rather than on an individual level and do not include personally identifiable information.

Because aggregated information does not include personal identifying information, it cannot be used to identify you. We may disclose aggregated data to third parties, such as advertisers, or include it in public records. 

With respect to [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie): We use cookies to track set user preferences however, all calculators will still work if you disable your cookies.

## Third Party Advertising

With respect to Ad Servers: When and if ads are present, we allow third-party companies to serve ads on our site pages. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information privacy policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.

Last updated: March 5, 2012
